[
    {
        "question": "Final methods can be overloaded.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "An anonymous class cannot have an explicitly declared constructor.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Java final class can be a superclass.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
    },
    {
        "question": "Methods that are declared as final or static cannot be overridden.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Super class reference variables can always point to subclass objects.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which data types the number 132 can fit?",
        "choices": ["int", "short", "long", "byte"],
        "type": "select",
        "correctAnswer": ["int", "short", "long"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The switch statement works with which of the following?",
        "choices": ["int", "String", "float", "long"],
        "type": "select",
        "correctAnswer": ["int", "String"]
    },
    {
        "question": "There can be only one public top-level class per .java file.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "int[] arr = {0,0,0,0,0};\nint x = 0;\nint y = 2;\nfor (int i = 0; i < 10; i +=2) {\n\tarr[x] = y + i;\n\tx++;\n}\nSystem.out.print(arr[3]);",
        "type": "input",
        "correctAnswer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "int arr[]={1, 2, 3, 4, 5};\nint x = 4;\nint y = 0;\nfor(int i = 0; i < 5; i++)\n\ty += arr[x - i] * i;\nSystem.out.print(y);",
        "type": "input",
        "correctAnswer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "for (int i = 1, j = 10; i < j; i += i, i++)\n\tSystem.out.print(j - i);",
        "type": "input",
        "correctAnswer": "9985"
    },
    {
        "question": "A method be private and abstract at the same time.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output?",
        "description": "int x = 17 * 71;\nboolean y = (x * 8 + x - 1) % x == x - 1;\nSystem.out.println(y);",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "main() can be overloaded in Java.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "We can create an object of the Math class.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
    },
    {
        "question": "Java supports default parameter values.",
        "choices": ["true", "false"],
        "type": "radio",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
    }
]